(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T12:43:06.969345",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ah, ah, ah, hello everybody!
Hi, can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Hello.
聞こえますか？
Can you hear me?
You can, you're acting like you can hear me.
Hello, oh hey, oh hey.
Now that's funny seeing you here, huh? Funny seeing me here.
Now that's funny seeing you here, huh?
Funny seeing me here.
Mm, huh?
Hmm, huh?
Happy birthday, Gura. Thank you!
That's right, today is my birthday,
my 9,000 bajillionth birthday.
Well, you guys, thank you!
Happy birthday, Guma. Thank you!
Happy birthday. Can't hear you.
Are you lying to me?
Okay. No, how would you be lying to me?
Well, thank you anyway! I hope you can hear me.
Happy birthday, Guma. Wow, look at that sea of green!
皆さんありがとうございます！
Thank you, everyone!
I wish we could change the color.
Imagine if we could change that to a sea of blue instead of a sea of green,
Imagine if we could change that to a sea
of blue instead of a sea of green,
that would be a lot more aesthetically pleasing for me, but I guess maybe not for everybody.
that would be a lot more aesthetically pleasing
for me, but I guess maybe not for everybody.
I'm sure Fauna really likes it when it's green instead of blue,
I'm sure Fauna really likes it when
it's green instead of blue,
but I don't know. Fauna, Fauna's cute.
So go I do... Um,
I'm nervous again,
but what is new? Uh you thought that was over,
but it's not.
I'm still incredibly nervous sitting here in my fish tube.
Actually, I was thinking about it,
me and this fish tube that I'm right here in, you know?
What if it's actually like just the very large intestine of a much larger fish?
That could potentially That could potentially be what the situation is.
What if we all are just in the large intestine of a much larger fish
on the earth? Like a meatball. Never mind, we don't have to talk about this anyway.
Thank you guys so much! Thank you!
Thank you, thank you for watching all of your birthday fan art is coming in you guys!
Thank you so much. I really appreciate
what everybody's been sending in.
I saw the bus! The good bus?
There's been the Goomba bus! Did you guys ride in the Goomba bus?
Did you get to sit inside the gar- girl bus?
Fill it with... gas?
New...
Anyway, it's really hard to see what you guys are saying,
cuz there's just so much burrr burr burr burr, which I appreciate, but um...
Anyway, I can
can you guys hear me though?
Okay, you can hear me.
We bussin'. We are bussin'.
We are fish- Do you think we can... Well, never mind.
What? There's a Goomba bus, there's a Goomba bus.
And I saw videos, there's a bunch of videos you guys, some animations as well.
Um, I want to say thank you for making me feel so special on my very special day.
Very, very special day.
What? Is the mic okay?
The mic is a peaky?
How wow? Hello?
What is wrong with the mic?
Can you? Mic is acting funny.
All great.
Um well, as you guys probably know,
well, I'm a little out of my element at the moment, so I would appreciate mic is peaking.
bbbbbbbb...
I see. I see what you mean.
Why is it doing that? I don't know why it's doing that.
I'll try not to overwhelm the microphone.
I will speak softer.
Okay, so um I hope you guys liked the streams yesterday.
They were a lot of fun.
Yeah, that was a lot of fun.
That actually it's still kind of sinking in what happened.
Robocura? What do you mean Robocura?
Did you like that?
Yeah, the karaoke was a lot of fun. I don't know how much I should say about it though.
Of course, I'm like absolutely filled to the brim with stuff that I want to talk about.
Well, um I made a night did.
Ah fuck. Ah. Yeah.
Yeah, she made me she made me a little cake, and she decorated it with white chocolate
and she made a little like sea creatures and she stuck it to the cake.
Um and the cake had had coffee in it, so after I ate it, I got really energized
cuz there was like espresso in it.
And um it really helped, I don't know, it helped me to stay awake
so I could see everything that you guys were sending me on Twitter with the hashtag, the birthday hashtag.
Um what else did we do? Oh, she made me dinner!
Yeah, she made me she made me dinner, she made me...
What just steak and rice, and and and broccoli, fancy broccoli, fancy broccoli.
But I ate really slow. Um I was kind of self-conscious about that, but um
it's okay, she eats slow too. She's not going to tell you that, but she eats pretty slow too, all right.
All right. And Watson eats her rice with soy sauce.
Did you know that? I prefer my rice plain,
uh just hot steam rice, plain, nothing on it.
Um but Watson likes to eat her rice with soy sauce.
Just a little thing, did you know that?
Hm? A slow eating competition?
Well, I was anxious,
um but also I do eat slowly. It's not a bad thing, is it? Do you guys eat fast or slow?
Soy sauce is pretty good. It is good, but the problem when you put well, soy sauce on rice
is that it makes it unsticky, so then you can't eat it very easily, so you have to eat it with a spoon or a straw or something, whatever you choose.
soy sauce, I don't know, just soy sauce.
Ever since soy sauce, if you guys eat baszo, don't you get like, I don't know, indigestion or something?
Anyway, though, I'll talk a bit more about the hanging out with Watson later.
Anyway, though, I'll talk a bit more about hanging out with Watson later.
Um, but first, I as being my birthday in Gura birthday tradition,
Um, but first, as being my birthday, in Gura birthday tradition,
I have a gift for you guys, a gift for all of you.
Um, you might guess what it is, but uh anyway,
Um, you might guess what it is, but anyway...
Um, so for all of you, uh I prepared a little something with the help of a very, very, very, very, very uh awesome uh artist that I I I really I look up to a lot.
Um, so for all of you, I prepared a little something with the help of a very, very, very awesome artist that I really look up to a lot.
Um, is it more streams? Yes. Um, but yes, but no, but yes, but not right now.
Um, is it more streams? Yes... but yes, but no, but yes, but not right now.
Um, so I have uh for you
Um, so I have... for you...
ta-da.
Tada!
New emotes!
And see, the cool thing about this is uh all of my do you see the shrimp emotes?
And see, the cool thing about this is all of my... do you see the shrimp emotes?
We have Eby emotes now.
We have now forever, what is it? immortalized
Eby in the emote list.
Let's take a look.
These are by Mariette.
Mariette. We have what do we have here?
Mariette. What do we have here?
Gura with a pen light that looks like a gun. That's actually I specifically I said, "Can you make Gura look like...
Gura with a pen light that looks like a gun. That's actually—I specifically asked, "Can you make Gura look like...
...can you make me look like I'm holding a gun, but instead of a gun, it's a it's a pen light?"
...can you make me look like I'm holding a gun, but instead of a gun, it's a pen light?"
Uh and then we have uh Neum, and then we have celebration,
And then we have Neum, and then we have celebration,
and then we have comfy Gura, and then we have Gura is dead,
and then we have comfy Gura, and then Gura is dead,
and then we have Gura is crying happy, and then we have Gura Gura is smiling at you very smug.
and Gura is crying happy, and Gura is smiling at you very smug.
And then we have squish the cheek of Gura, and then we have Gura scared.
And then we have squish the cheek of Gura, and Gura scared.
And then we have goo goo gura chat, and then we have Gura going hehehehehe, and then we have my face.
And then goo goo gura chat, and Gura going hehehe, and then my face—
for you guys do you guys are always looking at me funny. And then we have Gura hahaha!
you guys are always looking at me funny. And Gura hahaha!
And then we have Gura eyeball, and then we have Ebby.
And then Gura eyeball, and then Ebby.
Ebby chan!
Ebby-chan!
You guys are holding pen lights, you guys are looking at me like I probably just said something really awful and I don't realize it.
You guys are holding pen lights, looking at me like I probably just said something really awful and I don't realize it.
Um, and then you crying, and then your little face is like that.
And then you're crying, and your little face is like that.
When you say something stupid and don't realize it and I call you out, See?
Yeah! Okay, you should be able to use them now.
Can you use them now.
You can use them now.
There they are. Nice.
Excellent!
Look at all these Gura chats! Giga Gura chats!
and Mumei's the loading face, I always use that one, so I'm always looking excited to be able to get Mariette to help me out with these new emotes.
and Mumei's loading face, I always use that one, so I'm really excited to get Mariette to help with these new emotes.
Thank you Mariette if you're watching.
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Okay, so this this year I wanted to do something a little bit different than what we're I guess what I'm used to doing for birthdays,
Okay, so this year I wanted to do something a little bit different than what we're—I guess what I'm used to doing for birthdays,
or I mean I've only have one birthday, but I wanted to change it up a little bit this this year.
or I mean we only have one birthday, but I wanted to change it up a little bit this year.
You can't find Ebby? Ebby-chan, don't go!
Maybe there's a issue with Ebby Ebby-chan. Ebby-chan's coming? I was wondering why I couldn't see Ebby anywhere.
Maybe there's an issue with Ebby-chan. Ebby-chan's coming? I was wondering why I couldn't see Ebby anywhere.
I'm sure Ebby is coming. I'm sure Menezio is helping right now to make sure Ebby's working. No worries, Ebby's coming.
Maybe also refresh your page, that might be it.
But anyway, I want to talk about something that's going to happen. I wanted to do some stuff a little bit differently this year,
But anyway, I want to talk about something. I wanted to do some stuff a little bit differently this year,
but I still hope that you guys will like it.
Um, it took a lot of creative minds and patience and a lot of helping hands to make...
This... This uh, this year's birthday
This... This year's birthday
uh turned into something I think is really great
turned into something I think is really great,
and I I'm really excited for, and I
and I'm really excited for it.
probably am saying so much, um...
And I'm probably saying too much, um...
So... So, so, so.
How old am I now? Oh god.
How many times have I answered this question?
So many, so many times.
Please, not daki-makura.
Please, not a dakimakura.
You don't want a daki-makura.
That's right, there's merchandise!
Merchandise releases today!
Are you excited?
I'm really excited.
I I showed one of the other myth members the merchandise,
I showed one of the other Myth members
and she really liked it, so I hope you guys really like it as well.
the merch, and she really liked it,
so I hope you guys like it too.
Um... Okay.
Anyway, um, let's go.
And, uh, I didn't think I'd have to segue this at all whatsoever.
And I didn't think I'd have to segue
into this at all whatsoever.
Can you tell that I'm nervous?
Where's the shrimp emote?
I don't know. It should be coming anytime, though.
I don't know. It should be
coming anytime, though.
I need to hold I need to gather my thoughts. I'm really shaking right now.
I need to hold... gather my thoughts.
I'm really shaking right now.
The personality test that I took said that I do really well under pressure,
The personality test that I took
said I do really well under pressure,
and I think I do okay under pressure, but maybe not productively well.
and I think I do okay under pressure,
but maybe not productively well.
I just keep my cool, sort of. I think I keep my cool.
I just keep my cool, sort of.
I think I keep my cool.
Mic is funky.
It'll fix in a second. It's just suffering right now.
It'll fix in a second.
It's just suffering right now.
But anyway...
I want to sing some songs for you.
I want to I want to sing some music. That's that I know how to do that.
I want to sing some music.
That's... I know how to do that.
I'll do that for you guys because that'll help it calm me down and stuff.
I'll do that for you guys,
'cause that'll help calm me down.
Oh, Abby!
Oh, you look so good!
Look at it!
Oh, wow.
Abby.
Hello Ebb Abby one.
Hello Ab- Abby-one.
Cute.
Ah, it looks so good.
Okay, so yeah.
I want to I want to sing for you today because that's what I uh I like to do.
I want to sing for you today
because that's what I like to do.
It is an activity like we that we both like sharing in, right, you guys?
It's an activity that we
both like sharing in, right, you guys?
Uh, so...
But we're going to switch it up.
And um I hope you I hope I hope we have a good time today, okay? Are you ready to shake those pen lights?
And I hope we have a good time today, okay?
Are you ready to shake those pen lights?
Yeah. Okay.
Shall we ikou zo minna ikou zo...
Oh dear, what did I hit? Okay.
Minna. Okay. Okay.
Close your eyes, everybody.
Close them. Well, don't close them. Okay, yeah, close them now. Close.
Close 'em. Well, don't close 'em.
Okay, yeah, close 'em now. Close.
so much blue, it makes my heart so happy!
I love the color blue. Did you know that?
Okay. Um, anyway,
look at the big aquarium! Wow, fishies, fishy fishy.
look at the big aquarium!
Wow, fishies, fishy fishy.
And look at the floor! It's water. Water. Splashy splash.
And look at the floor! It's water.
Water. Splashy splash.
And look at me! That's right, I'm here too. Look at me!
And look at me! That's right,
I'm here too. Look at me!
I'm here, you're here, we're here.
Party! Yahoo! Pachi pachi pachi!
But first, I just want to say a big thank you to you guys.
But first, I just want to say
a big thank you to you guys.
To everybody, thank you. Thank you for supporting Shark
To everybody, thank you.
Thank you for supporting Shark
and believing in Shark.
Just sharky, little sharky.
All of this for little sharky, that's so crazy. Thank you guys so much.
All of this for little sharky,
that's so crazy. Thank you guys so much.
Ah, we also recently hit four bubu million subscribers, which is insanely...
Ah, we also recently hit four
booboo million subscribers, which is...
Um, also, I did some math...
insanely... Um, also, I did some math...
right, yeah, I know.
We're doing math, look out.
But roughly there are 15 shrimp to one pound,
so that technically means that with 4 million shrimp...
something, there's a big, there's a big shrimp lurking on the horizon is what I'm trying to say.
something, there's a big shrimp lurking on the horizon is what I'm trying to say.
And he's made up of millions, 4 million little tiny nano-shrimpies, that's all of you, you are building the giga-shrimp.
So we must be, we must be wary and look out for this very large specimen.
Um, you can do the exact math, though.
Uh, cuz I actually don't know how big this giga-shrimp is. Um, giga, mega, mega-shrimp.
Uh, 'cause I actually don't know how big this giga-shrimp is. Um, giga, mega, mega-shrimp.
Uh, I think I'm gonna stop myself here, though. Um, but anyways.
Okay, uh we all know that I cannot do math.
But I propose a counter offer.
But I propose a counter-offer.
Huh? You do the math? I'll do the singing.
I sing for you. I sing for you.
Um, I better start before I get too awkward, okay.
Uh, minna, start-o! This.
Uh, everyone, start! There.
なぜか「キミ」にだけ「ボク」が伝わらない
Why won't my "true self" reach just "you"?
募れば募るほどに苦しくなるよ
The more it grows, the more painful it gets.
“良薬は苦し”なんて笑って言っていたけれど
I used to laugh and say "good medicine tastes bitter," but
今更わかった
I finally understand now.
悪い夢なら醒めると願う日も
Even on days when I wish a bad dream would end,
誰にも言えない 秘密も
even secrets I can't tell anyone,
掛け違えたボタンもあの夜も
even mismatched buttons and that night—
幸せのレシピかもね
they might just be the recipe for happiness.
例えば「ボク」がボクじゃなければ
For instance, if "I" wasn't me,
「キミ」がキミじゃなければ…
or if "you" weren't you...
なんてでも記憶の一つ一つが
every single memory of why and how
「キミ」を呼ぶんだ
calls out for "you."
閉ざしていた日々と鎖していたココロ
Days I had shut away and a heart I had locked up,
魔法みたいに溶かしていく
melting them away like magic.
いろんな「キミ」がいる
There are all sorts of "you"s,
この世界が結局ほら、好きなんだ。
and in the end, look, I love this world.
なぜか「ボク」にだけ「キミ」がわからない
Why can't I understand "you" alone?
知ろうとするほどに難解なのさ
The more I try to know, the more baffling it is.
“案ずるより…”なんてわかっているつもりだけど
I feel like I know "better safe than sorry," but
今更言えない
I can't say it now.
態度の割に繊細なことも
How sensitive I am despite my attitude,
口は悪いけど優しいところも
how my mouth is harsh but my heart is kind,
照れ隠しのトゲも正義感も
the thorns of shyness and the sense of justice—
キミだけのレシピなんだ
they're recipes meant just for you.
例えば「ここ」がここじゃなければ
For instance, if "here" wasn't here,
「今」が今じゃなければ…
or if "now" wasn't now...
出会えてないそう想えばなんか
thinking we might never have met, somehow
悪くはないな
it's not so bad.
閉ざしていた過去と鎖していた明日は
A past I had closed off and a future I had locked away,
魔法みたいに繋いでく
connecting them together like magic.
幸せのレシピが溢れる
Recipes of happiness overflow,
世界がとってもほら、好きなんだ。
and look, I truly love this world.
戸惑いの今日のしるし
The proof of today's bewilderment,
もうひとつこぼれてるココロ
a heart overflowing with one more thing—
一つまみのジェラシー
a pinch of jealousy.
いつかみんな又逢って綺麗になりたい
Someday, we'll all meet again and become beautiful.
飛び切りの流星 おやすみのデュエット
A shooting star like no other, a duet before bedtime—
今夜はまどろみをほばって
tonight, let's embrace a bit more slumber.
夢とどくように
so that dreams may reach you.
キミと幸せのレシピで
With you, by the recipe of happiness,
幸せになりようよ
let's become happy!
キミと幸せのレシピで
With you, by the recipe of happiness,
幸せになろうよ
let's become happy!
キミをもっと味わいたい
I want to savor you even more.
幸せのレシピで
With the recipe of happiness,
キミをもっと味わいたい
I want to savor you even more.
幸せのレシピで
With the recipe of happiness,
幸せになろうよ
let's become happy!
幸せを作ってよ
Create happiness for me!
幸せのレシピで
With the recipe of happiness,
キミをもっと味わいたい
I want to savor you even more.
幸せのレシピで
With the recipe of happiness,
幸せになろうよ
let's become happy!
Let's become happy!
幸せのレシピで
With the recipe of happiness,
キミをもっと味わいたい幸せ
I want to savor you even more, happiness.
You know the recipe there.
しあわせのレシピ。達郎……達郎山下……
Recipe for Happiness... Tatsuro... Tatsuro Yamashita...
will forever be one of my favorite musical artists.
Seriously, I can always find a way to recommend people to listen to his music.
Wait, Guba! Guba, I don't know what to stream!
Wait, Gura! Gura, I don't know what to stream!
Aw, that sucks. Hey, we've heard this banger before.
Send the link. Send the link. Link, link, link.
I mean, I've already told you guys about how much I enjoy Tatsuro Yamashita's music, so...
So, you guys already know.
Actually, lately, my summer playlist has consisted of Tatsuro Yamashita's various albums, uh, and then Jeremy Soul as well.
Actually, lately, my summer playlist has consisted of Tatsuro Yamashita's various albums, uh, and then Jeremy Soule as well.
I have like two modes right now. It's either nostalgia for 1980s summer or or somewhere in a Skyrim tavern looking to pickpocket.
Do you guys smell that?
Do you smell that? It smells like... No, wait.
Nom nom. I can taste it too. It tastes like herbs and spices.
ゆらゆらゆら揺れている 乙女心ピン♡ピンチ!
Swaying, swaying, drifting, maiden's heart in a pinch!
かなりかなりヤバいのよ
Pretty dangerous, really dangerous
たすけてダーリン! クラクラリン
Help me, darling! I'm getting dizzy
何もかもが 新しい世界にきちゃったわ
Everything came to a brand-new world
たくさんのドキドキ乗っさい! 踏みさい! イクぞ!
Overcoming many heart-pounding moments, let's go!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
この想いは止められない
Can't stop this feeling of love
もっと乙女ちっく・パワー♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic power, sparkling
ちょっと危険なカ・ン・ジ
A little risky, but exciting
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
もう ドキドキ 止められない
Can't stop the excitement anymore
もっと ドラマティック・恋♪ ハレルヤ
More dramatic, love is clear
二人だけのバラライカ!
Our own balalaika!
すごく すごく 近づいて 乙女心チャ～ンス !
Getting closer, so close, maiden's heart has a chance!
ハート ハート 飛びだそう
Heart, heart, about to leap
おねがい ダーリン ! ハラハラ リン
Please, darling, heart pounding
あなた だけを 見つめてる ワタシ にしらんぷり ?
Only looking at you, I'm not playing hard to get?
気づいて ほしい のよ トキメキ ! ヤキモチ ! スキ よ !
I want you to notice the excitement, jealousy, and love!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
その 秘密 を おしえて よ
Tell me that secret
もっと 乙女 ちっく ・ モード ♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic mode, sparkling
やっぱ 笑顔 が ス ・ テ ・ キ
Smiling is the best
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
よそ見 し て ちゃ ダメダメ よ
No peeking, it's no good!
もっと ロマンティック ・ 恋 ♪ シャラ ランラン
More maiden-chic, love is shining
奏でたい の バラライカ !
I want to play the balalaika!
オンナ の コ は いつだって 夢見る 乙女 な の
Girls always dream in a pure heart
ピュアピュア な 心 で 恋して ! 愛して ! S ! O ! S !
Falling in love, loving, s-o-s!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
この 想い は 止められない
Can't stop this feeling of love
もっと 乙女 ちっく ・ パワー ♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic power, sparkling
ちょっと 危険 な カ ・ ン ・ ジ
A little risky, but exciting
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
もう ドキドキ 止められない
Can't stop the excitement anymore
もっと ドラマティック ・ 恋 ♪ ハレルヤ
More dramatic, love is clear
二人 だけ の バラライカ!
Our own balalaika!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
その 秘密 を おしえて よ
Tell me that secret
もっと 乙女 ちっく ・ モード ♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic mode, sparkling
やっぱ 笑顔 が ス ・ テ ・ キ
Smiling is the best
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
よそ見 し て ちゃ ダメダメ よ
No peeking, it's no good!
もっと ロマンティック ・ 恋 ♪ シャラ ランラン
More maiden-chic, love is shining
奏でたい の バラライカ !
I want to play the balalaika!
オンナ の コ は いつだって 夢見る 乙女 な の
Girls always dream in a pure heart
ピュアピュア な 心 で 恋して ! 愛して ! S ! O ! S !
Falling in love, loving, s-o-s!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
この 想い は 止められない
Can't stop this feeling of love
もっと 乙女 ちっく ・ パワー ♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic power, sparkling
ちょっと 危険 な カ ・ ン ・ ジ
A little risky, but exciting
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
もう ドキドキ 止められない
Can't stop the excitement anymore
もっと ドラマティック ・ 恋 ♪ ハレルヤ
More dramatic, love is clear
二人 だけ の バラライカ!
Our own balalaika!
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
その 秘密 を おしえて よ
Tell me that secret
もっと 乙女 ちっく ・ モード ♪ きらりりんりん
More maiden-chic mode, sparkling
やっぱ 笑顔 が ス ・ テ ・ キ
Smiling is the best
バラライカ バララライカ バラ ラライ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalalalai ka, bala lailai kaikai!
よそ見 し て ちゃ ダメダメ よ
No peeking, it's no good!
もっと ロマンティック ・ 恋 ♪ シャラ ランラン
More maiden-chic, love is shining
奏でたい の バラライカ !
I want to play the balalaika!
バラライカ
Balalaika
ゆらりゆらり揺れている少女心ピンチ!
Swaying back and forth, a maiden's heart is at its limit!
かなりかなりヤバイのよ
This is pretty dangerous, isn't it?
たすけてダーリン! クラクラリン
Help me, darling! Cling-clang-clinging!
何もかもが新しい世界にきちゃったわ
Everything has burst into a brand new world!
たくさんのドキドキ乗り越え! 踏み越え! イイクぞ!
Ride over all the excitement! Step right over it! Let's go!
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
この想いは止められない
I can't stop these feelings.
もっと少女チック。パワー キラリリン
With a bit more maiden chic power,
ちょっと危険なカ・ン・ジ
It's a slightly dangerous feeling.
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
もうドキドキ止められない
I can't stop this racing heart anymore.
もっとドラマチック。恋 ハレルヤ
A more dramatic, loving hallelujah!
ふたり だけ の バラライカ!
Our very own balalaika!
すごくすごく近づいて乙女心チャンス!
Getting closer and closer, it's a maiden's chance!
ハートハート飛び出そう
My heart is about to leap right out!
お願いうだーリン! ハラハラリン
Please, darling! Flutter-flutter-fluttering!
あなただけを見つめているあたしに知らんぷり?
Are you pretending not to notice me gazing only at you?
気づいてほしいのよ トキメキ! ヤキモキ! スキ ヨ!
I want you to realize it. I'm thrilled! Impatient! In love!
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
その秘密を教えてよ
Tell me what that secret is!
もっと少女チック。モード キラリリン やっぱ笑顔がス・テ・キ
With more maiden chic power, you're wonderful!
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
よそ見してちゃダメダメよ
Don't you dare look away from me!
もっとロマンチック 恋 シャラ ランラ
A more romantic, sha-ran-ran love!
奏でたい の バラライカ
I want to play our balalaika!
女の子 は いつだって 夢見る 少女 なの
Girls are always dreaming,
ピュアピュア な 心 で 恋して 愛して s.o.s
Loving and adoring with a pure heart, S.O.S.!
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
この 想い は 止め られない
I can't stop these feelings.
もっと 少女 チック パワー
With a bit more maiden chic power,
キラ リリン ちょっと 危険 な カンジ
It's a slightly dangerous feeling.
バラライカ バララライカ バラライラ カイカイ!
Balalaika, balalaika, balala-laika-kai-kai!
もう ドキドキ 止め られない
I can't stop this racing heart anymore.
もっと ドラマチック 恋 ハレルヤ
A more dramatic, loving hallelujah!
ふたり だけ の バラライカ!
Our very own balalaika!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
誰にも負けないあなたに世界で一番一番一番一番!
I won't lose to anyone, we're number one in this world!
恋してる!
Falling in love with you!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
ほらキャッチュ キャッチュ キャッチュミ キャッチュミ 絶対
Hooray, catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me! Never let me go!
運命だって お似合いだって
Destiny, even our compatibility is meant to be!
そうマジで中吉ーグッドトゥーシーユーきっと!
So it must mean we're good to see, you got it!
誰にも負けないあなたに世界で一番一番一番一番!
I won't lose to anyone, we're number one in this world!
恋してる!
Falling in love with you!
君とのラブストーリー それは予想通り
Our love story was just as expected.
いざ始まれば ひとり芝居だ
Once it began, it was a one-man show.
ずっとそばにいたって
Even though I was always by your side,
結局 ただの観客だ
In the end, I was just a spectator.
感情のないアイムソーリー それはいつもの通り
An emotionless, routine "I'm sorry."
慣れてしまえば悪くはないけど
Once you get used to it, it's not so bad.
青巻き紙 赤巻き紙 きまきゃきゃ
Blue wrapping paper, red wrapping paper, kimakyakya
気持ちが きゃんと伝えられない
I can't convey my feelings properly
もう 勘弁死刑
Seriously, this is death by embarrassment!
また噛んじゃった
I bit my tongue again
生麦生米 なうまみゃ
Raw wheat, raw rice, namamamya
頭が 不安でいっぱいです
My head is full of anxiety
ねえ 神様おねがいしょまつ
Hey, God, I beg you...
また噛んじゃった
I bit my tongue again
東京特許 許可局 許可局
Tokyo patent office, permit bureau
共有羞恥
Shared embarrassment
はあ あいつの失敗は
Ha, when others fail
横目で笑えるのに
We can just laugh it off out of the corner of our eyes
東京特許 許可局 許可局
Tokyo patent office, permit bureau
今日はもうやだ
Today is just the worst
自分のミスは笑えないんです
But I can't laugh at my own mistakes
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
何千回迷惑かけちゃってごめんね
Sorry for causing trouble thousands of times
普通に生きるって難しいんですよね
Living normally is so difficult, isn't it?
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
舌を噛み噛み ガミガミ言わないで
Bite your tongue, don't nag me!
怒りカリカリ カリ・ユガの時代で
Boiling with anger in the age of Kali Yuga
舌を噛み噛み ぎゃむっとまた噛んで
Bite your tongue, I tripped over my words again!
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
君を愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ また嫌われちゃった
Loving you, loving you, loving you, and you ended up hating me again
どうしよう どうする 老若男女轟く感動
What should I do? What do I do? Emotions shaking all ages
私一文無し 感度ゼロあーもうどうしよう
I'm penniless, zero sensitivity, ah geez what do I do
だって庭には鳥二億羽と監視カメラ
Because in the yard there are two hundred million birds and security cameras
バスヴァス爆発 精神崩壊の過剰過敏
Bus vase explosion, oversensitivity of mental collapse
ねえ 私は何処へ異教か また噛んじゃった
Hey, where am I converting? I bit my tongue again
隣の客はよく かきょきゃく クレーム言う星 人
The customer next door often complains, an alien of complaints
言ってる事がちゃんと伝わらない
What I'm trying to say isn't getting across properly
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
何千回迷惑かけちゃってごめんね
Sorry for causing trouble thousands of times
普通に生きるって難しいんですよね
Living normally is so difficult, isn't it?
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
舌を噛み噛み ガミガミ言わないで
Bite your tongue, don't nag me!
怒りカリカリ カリ・ユガの時代で
Boiling with anger in the age of Kali Yuga
舌を噛み噛み ぎゃむっとまた噛んで
Bite your tongue, I tripped over my words again!
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
君を信じちぇ 信じちぇ 信じちぇ また裏切られた
Believing in you, believing in you, believing in you, and I was betrayed again
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
何千回迷惑かけちゃってごめんね
Sorry for causing trouble thousands of times
普通に生きるって難しいんですよね
Living normally is so difficult, isn't it?
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
舌を噛み噛み ガミガミ言わないで
Bite your tongue, don't nag me!
怒りカリカリ カリ・ユガの時代で
Boiling with anger in the age of Kali Yuga
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
何千回迷惑かけちゃってごめんね
Sorry for causing trouble thousands of times
普通に生きるって難しいんですよね
Living normally is so difficult, isn't it?
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
舌を噛み噛み ガミガミ言わないで
Bite your tongue, don't nag me!
怒りカリカリ カリ・ユガの時代で
Boiling with anger in the age of Kali Yuga
舌を噛み噛み ぎゃむっとまた噛んで
Bite your tongue, I tripped over my words again!
いていていて
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
あまがみ 噛みで おねがい
Soft bite, a soft bite please
君を愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ まだ嫌われてない
Loving you, loving you, loving you, and you still don't hate me
愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ
Loving you, loving you, loving you
ああもう一回
Ah, once more!
愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ 愛しちぇ
Loving you, loving you, loving you
ああまた言えなかった
Ah, I couldn't say it again
愛してる 愛してる 愛してる
I love you, I love you, I love you
言ってしまった
I ended up saying it
でも君はもういない
But you're no longer here
眠れないよ 頭中君だけだ
Can't sleep, my mind is full of just you
君のせいでこんな夜 yeah yeah yeah
Because of you, a night like this yeah yeah yeah
12時鳴り響いた教会 気づけば通り過ぎてる
The clock strikes twelve in the church, before you even notice.
見つけた摩訶不思議の正体 逃げたらお仕置きするぞ
We found the mysterious entity, try to run and you'll be punished!
ほらほらさあお菓子を頂戴 お菓子をちょーだい
Come on, give me some treats! (Treats, gimme treats!)
くれたらいいたずらするぞ いたずらするぞ
Or I'll play a trick on you! (I'll play a trick on you!)
いつでもほら準備は万端 まだまだ夜は長いぞ
Always prepared, the night is still young!
君は全然なってない trick or treat
You're not doing it right at all, trick or treat.
それじゃ真っ逆さまじゃん fall in night
So instead, fall right into the night!
I will give you all my love
なぜか優しい気持ちが あふれ初めてのチュウ
Why is everyone so kind and lovely tonight?
君とチュウ I will be in love with you
Falling in love with you!
Hey, is that true or false, fish brain?
ねえもっと楽しもう もう決めたんだ
Let's have fun together, we've already decided!
明日の夢へと膨らんでくる
Tomorrow's dreams will surely swell up!
この愛を to you いつまでも to you
This love will overflow for you!
きっと きっと きっとさ
Surely, surely, come on!
はじめてのチュウ 君とチュウ I will give you all my love
First time in love, giving you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが あふれ初めてのチュウ
Why is everyone so kind and lovely tonight?
君とチュウ I will be in love with you
Falling in love with you!
Hey, is that true or false, fish brain?
ねえもっと楽しもう もう決めたんだ
Let's have fun together, we've already decided!
明日の夢へと膨らんでくる
Tomorrow's dreams will surely swell up!
この愛を to you いつまでも to you
This love will overflow for you!
きっと きっと きっとさ
Surely, surely, come on!
はじめてのチュウ 君とチュウ I will give you all my love
First time in love, giving you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが あふれ初めてのチュウ
Why is everyone so kind and lovely tonight?
君とチュウ I will be in love with you
Falling in love with you!
Hey, is that true or false, fish brain?
ねえもっと楽しもう もう決めたんだ
Let's have fun together, we've already decided!
明日の夢へと膨らんでくる
Tomorrow's dreams will surely swell up!
この愛を to you いつまでも to you
This love will overflow for you!
きっと きっと きっとさ
Surely, surely, come on!
はじめてのチュウ 君とチュウ I will give you all my love
First time in love, giving you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが あふれ初めてのチュウ
Why is everyone so kind and lovely tonight?
君とチュウ I will be in love with you
Falling in love with you!
Hey, is that true or false, fish brain?
ねえもっと楽しもう もう決めたんだ
Let's have fun together, we've already decided!
明日の夢へと膨らんでくる
Tomorrow's dreams will surely swell up!
この愛を to you いつまでも to you
This love will overflow for you!
Trick or treat
Your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight
No way to stop, she's dead set on giving you a fright
Trick or treat, but now we're all out of candy
Feeling just a little sick, this jeans' out of handy
I got a fairy, just possessed, so let's experiment
Out drop the little babies, hiding behind your screens
Today is spooky Halloween without the mythical beings
Cat is blushing, look at those red cheeks
I'll fix that up, drain all your love ex-wah-you-see
You see
Myth or treat!
Oh, what a cursified stream
There's no bones about it, you'll scream
Only show ya on Halloween,
Our spookier, terrifying, scarier sides
Oh, what a gachikoi night,
Mythic witches with endless spite
Can't escape our idol-esque might
No candy in sight, so your souls will suffice
Bust a funky dance tonight
What a spooky scary sight
Hungry dinosaur, just one tiny bite, please
Spook our viewers with a song, if you're brave, then sing along
Not your "wife," I am a pumpkin, ding-dong
In the graveyard we will be, if you're looking for a scream
Singing songs that make you pee a-r-t-y
Give you shivers, make you shout
Just like that, now myth is out, spooky ladies, that is what we're about
Ah, I love singing with the other members and me with wah. Hope you guys liked it too.
I really, really appreciate everybody's hard work to make today happen.
It's a really nice feeling knowing that I can rely on my friends and other shubrigade people to make such fun experiences happen for all of you.
It's a really nice feeling knowing that I can rely on my friends and other Shubberigade people to make such fun experiences happen for all of you.
I'm so very grateful, so thank you. Thank you everybody, and also each of you.
Thank you for your patience and your incredible support. Another year of shark.
I'm so lucky to be surrounded by such dedicated folks like you. Thank you everybody. Thank you.
Now, more fun stuff, birthday stuff!
Merchandise, baby, merchandise! Give me the goods, shark.
Give me the goods. I know, I know, I know. I'm so excited about this year's merch.
I seriously love it so much. I've been looking at pictures of it every day leading up to this exact moment, hoping all of you will be just as excited as I am.
Drumroll, mina.
Drumroll, everyone.
Goodbye merch! Wow, goodbye!
On sale pretty soon. I don't know exactly when, but whatever. Anyways, cute!
Cute, cute, cute. First, let's start with adorable art by Ponkkan.
Featuring Ebi-chan and hydrangea, my favorite summer flower, because it's all blue and there's water.
And I'm so cute with my little sailor outfit. I'm so cute! I'm so cute, how I mentioned how cute? I'm so cute!
And I'm so cute with my little sailor outfit. I'm so cute! I'm so cute, have I mentioned how cute? I'm so cute!
I love this art so much. And the good thing is is that it's available as a postcard. Limited complete sets will include a hand-signed signature by me, Goobagoobagabagoobi.
I love this art so much. And the good thing is that it's available as a postcard. Limited complete sets will include a hand-signed signature by me, Goobagoobagabagoobi.
And this art will also be available as a rubber mat!
It's grippy, perfect for high-octane activities like like Gundam building.
It's grippy, perfect for high-octane activities like Gundam building.
And bonus points because it's cute. It's cute. I wonder if you can do other things on it like gaming, maybe? I don't know, just don't get it dirty. Well, you can get it dirty if you want, you know, it's all right. It's cute!
And bonus points because it's cute. It's cute. I wonder if you can do other things on it like gaming, maybe? I don't know, just don't get it dirty. Well, you can get it dirty if you want. It's all right. It's cute!
Okay, next up. I don't think you guys are ready for this.
Dino Gura! Dino Gura! It's here!
Has super round tummy, little round yellow toes and scales, and an embroidered ebi on the tushie, designed by none other than Saminco.
Has a super round tummy, little round yellow toes and scales, and an embroidered ebi on the tushie, designed by none other than Saminco.
Dino Gura is real. Dino Gura, you can own a Dino Gura. Dino Gura can now peacefully live in your home, just for you. And you can pull the hood down and reveal my twin tails.
I'm squishy,
it's punchable,
it's puntable,
And I might have cried when I first saw the plushie designs,
because, well my uncle is such a god at creating
cute things, designing anything and everything that's
cute. My uncle is number one.
I hope you will give Dino Gura a good home.
Also while I'm here, can somebody make
the Luigi centrifuge meme video, but it's like Dino Guba instead?
Uh maybe I'll do it. I can do it.
Instead of... it'll be me, but I'll be doing
something else.
We're not done yet.
Then we have...
the Guba bowl.
I am absolutely dead serious when I say that kitchenware is my weakness,
also designed by same-uncle.
The Guba bowl features me, peeking,
and bloop at the very bottom of the bowl, ensuring that no crumbs are left behind.
Do you see how cute this bowl is?
I love kitchen I love kitchenware.
I love kitchenware. Kitchenware daisuki.
In fact, I want more. I need a myth like a myth dinnerware set.
I need bowls, I need plates, I need cups. We have cups.
Well now I need the rest of it. We need bowls.
More bowls, I say. Give me more bowls, please.
I won't even use them. I will just... I just want to look at them. Just let me look at them.
There's more, guys.
To go alongside your very own Garga bowl.
Trident fork. Trident chopsticks. I repeat, trident fork, trident chopsticks.
It's blue, well turquoise. Turquoise blue.
I've I've talked to you guys about how much I wanted to make a trident fork.
Okay, I wanted it to be glowing. This one doesn't glow, but still, look at it.
Trident cutlery set, holy moly motherload. Trident fork and chopsticks set.
Designed by yours truly, that's right I designed because we talked about it. Remember you guys?
Uh yeah, not quite as powerful as my own trident, but definitely strong enough to lift your favorite meal into your mouse.
Uh yeah, not quite as powerful as my own trident, but definitely strong enough to lift your favorite meal into your mouth.
Lift your favorite meal out of the Guba bowl and into your mouse.
Lift your favorite meal out of the Guba bowl and into your mouth.
And lastly... a voice pack, the... featuring some notification sounds
And lastly... a voice pack, featuring some notification sounds
that you can use in whichever device you wish to gurafy. Your PC, your phone,
your iPads, your your I devices. Can I say iPad on stream? I just said iPad.
your iPads, your I devices. Can I say iPad on stream? I just said iPad.
Any device that you would like my voice coming out of that accepts audio.
Uh now, okay, I will say that there are more things in the oven currently,
but they need a bit more time. Just a bit.
Uh and I hope I hope you look forward to what I'm cooking up.
Thank you guys for coming to my birthday party this year.
I I hope you had a nice time.
I hope you like the goods. I hope you like the songs.
Thank you Myth for singing with me and for uh hanging out with me on my birthday.
Thank you Myth for singing with me and for hanging out with me on my birthday.
I'm very lucky to be surrounded by such a talented group of group of ladies.
I'm very lucky to be surrounded by such a talented group of ladies.
And I appreciate and uh cherish every moment that we've been able to spend together on this this holo live journey.
And I appreciate and cherish every moment that we've been able to spend together on this hololive journey.
Thank you guys. The same to you guys as well watching this journey. Let's see where we go next, right?
It is time for me to go, but I'll see you again real soon, okay?
Ookie dokie everybody.
Bye everybody
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye-bye!
Bye, bye, bye, bye